So let's take a look at the same fate?
Let's take a look at our wishes.
We are one of them.
What's that?
There's a gigantic storm called Aqua
Laguna that's on its way here right now?
That's right!
By midnight tonight,
this entire beach will be completely
underwater as well as half of the town!
Crazy, huh?
That's terrible!
We should get out of here right away!
Yes, sir!
If we were smart, that's
exactly what we would do!
Let's evacuate to higher
ground! Good idea!
Let's do that!
Evacuate!
That's weird.
I could have sworn they
hurt someone out here!
Be sure to evacuate.
Evacuate, stop!
They were saying something about a storm?
Well, actually, the wind is
awfully strong, isn't it?
I'm telling you people, we
didn't do anything wrong!
You're making a mistake!
And why should we trust anything you say?
You scumbags are pirates
and probably assassins, too!
This doesn't even make any sense!
There's no reason why
Robin would attack him!
Yeah!
Not only that, we'd never even heard
of Iceberg until we met him yesterday!
You brats just keep
saying that all you want.
It's over.
Fact is, you picked on the wrong guy.
The moral of the story is, if
you make an enemy out of Iceberg,
then you make an enemy out of
the entire Galilag Company.
And that's not the half of it.
You also made an enemy out of
everyone in this whole city.
You understand?
Listen, I don't want to fight any of you.
We can still talk about all this, okay?
I don't give a damn what you want.
That's what you get for
messing with Kali-Lot!
What's the matter, Straw Hat?
You're not even gonna go out with a fight?
I just told you!
We're not enemies and I don't
want to fight any of you!
Since pistols don't work on you,
we'll have to go with plan B.
Damn it all!
I guess these guys are going all out, huh?
No, he got away.
Wow, they almost had me.
Oh, I can't dodge anymore!
Yeah, that's right!
All right, nice shot!
Yeah!
And that's why Galley-La
are pride and joy! Woo!
It feels good to see them lose.
I hope they blow that
sorry sucker sky high!
Nah, I shouldn't say that after
all Straw Hats, our enemy, too,
and I haven't beaten him
nearly enough, not yet.
And to be fair, I was here first.
Wasn't I I?
I enjoyed your little show, but this is
my stage and the only star here is Franky.
So get out of my!
Hold your horses we'll
be done with them in a
second then you can fight
us to your heart's content.
Listen you I called dibs on straw
hat before all of you even got here?
No, screw it.
You don't even care what I say, do you?
Paulie, watch out!
Get out of there!
Frankie's going nuts again!
Run away!
Huh?
Connector set.
He brought down a crane with
that attack. It's lethal!
That was him?
Looks like a cannon hit it.
He's about to fire!
Get him broke!
Your cannon's ready to go!
Hey!
Don't expect me to shoot
a cannonball or anything.
The shells I fire are
made of nothing but air.
Still, these babies
break the speed of sound.
Air, huh?
Run for your lives!
What the hell?
Man, he was a kitten.
That thing hits like a
hurricane to the face.
Another brain is coming down!
Get out of here!
It's gonna fall on us!
Hurry up!
Here it comes!
Yeah, let it fall!
Hell, I don't care.
Let's bring the whole damn shipyard down!
He really is a cyborg.
I thought he was kidding.
But that air shot was no joke.
I've never even seen technology like that.
But hey.
No more angry mom. At least.
Nami, run!
Luffy, you didn't get
hit back there, did you?
It's gonna take a lot more than that
if those guys want to get rid of me.
Okay, come on.
We gotta get going.
I'm not sure how, but we
gotta talk to Ice Pops.
What? Now?
When the whole town is
out searching for us?
Hey, look!
Straw Hat's getting away!
Uh-oh.
They're trying to surround us.
Nami!
Hey, hold on tight, okay?
No, not okay!
Stop them!
They're too fast!
Follow them!
Bro?
They're getting away, don't
you want to go after them?
Ah, that last coup de vin
did ate up all my fuel.
You see this?
My pompadour's limp.
No kidding.
It looks like a willow
swaying in the wind.
What a mess, stupid Galley-La.
But I'll take care of that straw
hat as soon as I'm done refueling.
That kid ain't half bad, you know?
He certainly earned his big bounty.
Jeez Louise.
Even for Franky, this is too much.
Today just isn't our day.
Franky or no Franky, we
can't let Straw Hat escape.
Aqua Laguna is gonna hit tonight.
There are only two sea
train departures left today.
Since the Straw Hats
can't leave on their ship,
the Sea Train's the only ticket
they've got to get off the island.
This is our chance.
Have every member of Galley-La
spread out and hunt them down.
We'll settle this before sunset.
Granny, look!
It's Water 7!
Don't get too excited and
fall in the ocean now.
If that isn't Galley-La
HQ, I don't know what is.
No surprise, since it's right
next to Dock 1. And look!
The place is totally
swarming with reporters.
Those tough-looking guys
are probably shipwrights.
I'm willing to bet that's
where Iceberg's at.
You sure about this?
Of course, I am.
The only way for me to
find out what's going on
between Ice Pops and Robin
is to ask him myself.
I can't stop you,
but you should keep in
mind that everyone on
the island is trying to
hunt us down right now.
So listen before you do anything rash.
Sneak around and figure
out where Icebergs'
room is so you know where you need to go.
All right. I'm off.
What? No!
They can't find them.
Who's that?
Wait, it can't be!
Someone broke the window!
We're under attack!
Straw Hat Luffy broken!
He must be after Iceberg!
He's doing this in the middle of the day?
He's got some guts coming after us now.
Where is he?
He's taking the stairs
up to the third floor.
Where are the foremen?
They all spread out
looking for Straw Hats.
No one is here.
He's wearing a red vest.
You can't miss him.
Don't let him get to Iceberg.
I found us.
Hey, over here.
Where is he?
Don't shoot a pistol,
you idiot! We're inside!
You're gonna disturb Mr.
Iceberg!
I know you need to rest.
I apologize for the commotion.
Well, what's going on?
Apparently, Straw Hat Luffy has
broken in and is running amok.
In that case, I have a plan.
Found him!
Whoa, there's a lot of shipwrites!
He's going to building two!
Follow him!
Lupi, wait!
It's you!
Khalifa, did you see a
pirate come this way?
If I had, then you'd know.
And by the way, you're far too noisy. Mr.
Iceberg still needs his peace and quiet.
You're right.
Sorry.
Looks like the Straw Hat
hasn't made it this far yet.
Let's stay and watch around this hallway.
This is where he's headed for sure.
Well hello there, pirate boy.
Were you looking for me?
Sure was.
Thanks for saving me from those guys.
Considering the angry mob, I assume that
you didn't burst in here just to murder me.
All I want is to hear
your side of the story.
Last night I saw Nico Robin here.
Without a doubt.
And mind you, I have
nothing against any of you.
I have no reason to lie.
Are you sure it wasn't
someone who looked like her?
Shut up and listen, boy.
I didn't call you in here to
bicker about who did what.
I have a favor to ask, and it would
be in your best interest to grant it.
No matter what it takes.
I have to see Niko-Robin again.
We're here! We're here!
Come on, Granny! Hurry! Hurry! Calm down.
Get a hold of yourself.
Water 7.
It's been a while. Granny!
Hurry! Hurry! Okay! Okay!
Attention all passengers!
Wearing a mask on the Sea Train
today is strictly prohibited.
Look, ma 'am, just cooperate
and show me your face.
This is my face. See?
Hey, you.
Oh, uh, Miss Kokoro.
So nice to see you again.
What's going on here, trouble?
Yes, yes, ma 'am.
Everyone is on the lookout
for the Straw Hat Pirates,
the culprits in the attempted
assassination of Iceberg.
Iceberg's assassins?
What is it, Granny? Huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
I'll say it once again!
Let me see, Nico Robin?
Sorry, that's not possible.
We have no idea where she is.
Gunfire!
It came from the bedroom!
Icebird! We heard it!
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'd hoped to come closer to the truth.
But that foolish hope has been in vain.
Arrest all of the Straw Hat Pirates.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Luffy.
Were you able to speak with Iceberg?
What did he say?
Is it true? Yeah.
He said it was Robin,
no doubt of it. No way.
Why would she do something like that?
I refuse to believe it.
Hey there, welcome. How are you? Ow!
How's everything going, Blueno?
Feeling super!
Yeah, well, I suppose you could say that.
What do you mean suppose
you're not a very decisive
guy are you I'll take
the usual fill her up,
please Do you got any money?
Just fill them up. Will ya?
Cola Yeah,
I think you're running an
establishment like this with
a greedy notion of taking
money from your customers.
We do have a little money a million
berries left from our shopping spree.
We have that much left so disgraceful?
I'm totally Uncle to think that I
didn't spend it all in one night.
Here, give me that.
Wow, listen up.
This is your lucky day, customers.
All your drinks are on me, not
back as much booze as you like.
Compliments of me, your pal Franky.
Hey, that's our Franky.
You're the best.
The face of one or seven's
underworld. What a guy.
Whoa, that's awesome.
Look over here.
It's palatable.
So, Bluno, where's my cola?
Come on, hurry it up already.
Looks like business has
been good for you, Franky.
Old Hat Kokoro, that
was you I sat next to?
I thought it was a
statue of a sea monster.
Granny, is it okay for me to
get a refill of my juice then?
Hey, kid, this is a bar.
It's no place for little shrimps like you.
Business has been good, right?
Fine, whatever suit yourself.
Yeah, business has been
outstanding, but I feel terrible!
In fact, this entire week
has been a total downer?
And it's all because of
that stupid pirate here!
You go, full tank! Good!
Took you long enough?
Super!
There!
Completely restored!
That bastard, wait till
I get my hands on him!
Hey, Hag, why are you here?
Aqua Laguna is on its way.
Oh, is that right?
No wonder the wind's
blowing so strong today.
You need to get your house
prepped up for the storm. Well,
there's nothing much to prep, really,
seeing as how I don't
actually have a house anymore.
I was going to have a drink with
Iceberg, but it seems he was shot.
Yeah, I heard about that.
They say pirates are responsible.
Galley-La and the townspeople
are raging pissed.
So a pirate did it, huh?
Do you honestly think
that's what happened?
Hey, you sound like you know something.
If you really do, then
spit it out, you old hag.
Iceberg's constantly being
hounded by the world government.
You ever notice that? So?
Wait, are you trying to say that
government lapdog Corgi pulled the trigger?
That little troll isn't cut
out to try something like that.
You're right.
That assassination plot falls
more in line with the work of CP9.
Is that right, Belt?
Ever heard of him?
Eh, lonely rumors, really.
Jeez,
you village simpletons sure
put a lot of stock into
stories about imaginary
boogeyman shadow organizations.
Don't be an idiot.
Of course they exist.
They just never show themselves.
Can't really work undercover
if everyone knows who you are.
You seem pretty sure of yourself.
Got some kind of proof about this?
Nope, just rumors.
Stop screwing around, hag!
Look, rumors are superstitious nonsense!
Gosh, they've remained a rumor
for such a long time, huh?
They're good at eliminating
people without anyone noticing.
If you mess with them, you're dead meat.
Impressive work.
The assignment we had to do
yesterday went very well.
Excellent job, Nico Robin.
Thanks, it was a cakewalk.
Though naturally, you're now being
pursued by every last person in the city.
Indeed I am.
Merely a temporary setback.
Tonight is what's important.
Understand?
We'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residents one more time.
If it becomes a worst-case scenario, you're
free to eliminate all of the evidence.
Among Tom's apprentices who could
have had it from the very beginning,
Iceberg is the only
one that remains alive.
No matter how much he denies having it in
the name of Cape, we will take it tonight.
Never forget, this is
a mission of justice.